<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Nishith</title>
    <link>https://nishithblog.ml/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Nishith</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 18:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nishithblog.ml/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>100&#43; Medium Followers in 2022 and Making an Online Presence 👨‍💻</title>
      <link>https://nishithblog.ml/posts/2022-01-16-100-medium-followers-making-online-presence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishithblog.ml/posts/2022-01-16-100-medium-followers-making-online-presence/</guid>
      <description>Hey Readers! Happy New Year 🎉 and Let’s make this year count!
I wish everyone a great year ahead and may you never stopping dreaming!
Every year I make some resolutions to become a better version of myself. Past years have been difficult for all us and these goals help me keep moving forward. Here are some of my previous year’s resolutions and their final outcome (Spoiler: I’m not perfect):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Vs. R… long lasting debate simplified</title>
      <link>https://nishithblog.ml/posts/2022-01-02-python-vs-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishithblog.ml/posts/2022-01-02-python-vs-r/</guid>
      <description>What programming language to choose for Data Science and Machine Learning.
This article won’t bore you with the stats of the most used programming language in a year or the languages that recruiters or companies prefer, because in order to get a great Data Science job, one must know both languages to some extent and really master one of the two.
This article will try to help you to choose the language to start with or the one to master.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make your Windows PC Faster and Smoother</title>
      <link>https://nishithblog.ml/posts/2021-08-08-making-windows-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishithblog.ml/posts/2021-08-08-making-windows-faster/</guid>
      <description>An article written by an eight year old PC to help it’s successors lead a better life.
Windows 11 is on the horizon and most of the people are excited to get a worthy update, but not every PC in the market is eligible for Windows 11 upgrade (not even a 3 year old hardware) due to some security requirements which Microsoft thinks are crucial for running Windows 11. So, we have to run Windows 10 till these requirement issues are sorted out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I got started with Data Science for Free!</title>
      <link>https://nishithblog.ml/posts/2021-08-01-getting-started-with-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nishithblog.ml/posts/2021-08-01-getting-started-with-data-science/</guid>
      <description>An article on free tools and a roadmap to start learning Data Science/ Machine Learning with no programming experience.
Disclaimer This article reflects my thoughts and experience of pursuing Data Science. I am not a big fan of overly priced MOOCs or online courses and their promise of becoming a successful Data Scientist within months or weeks. Don’t get me wrong, these courses can help you with the basic idea of what is Data Science, and the technologies used but they will never be able to make you a master nor will you be able to get good high paying jobs based solely on these courses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
